Ah, everyone!
I can see it! I could see it! I could see it!
I got to see it. Hey, that's too good.
It's too hard.
I know it's not that hard.
I'm glad I saw it.
I'm so glad.
I'd like to do karaoke again later today.
So please think of a song you'd like me to sing.
I've been wanting to tell you that story... so I thought I'd do it today...
But... what?
Well, the three of us originally talked about going together.
So we made a plan.
We made plans, and we went, and we decided to go, and we decided to do a little bit of cutie cutie cutie. Do you want to go together? But in the end...
We decided not to match, and everyone wore their favorite catsuits.
We all wore whatever we wanted, and we all wore whatever we wanted, but we all looked pretty much the same.
It was a lot of fun.
I wrote about it on my Instagram.
That's how we all go to Disney, right?
That's why I put it on my Instagram.
I wanted to post about it on SNS.
So we said, "Let's take a lot of pictures together.
We were talking about it.
But when we got back...
We have our cell phones, so we made an album with all the pictures we took.
There are so few!
I really, really, really...
I thought I had taken more, but I didn't take any.
I was so surprised.
I wrote about it on my Instagram, but you know what the three of us were saying at the end?
"Let's ride more than just pictures.
Indiana Jones?
I'm not very good at remembering names.
I'm not very good at remembering names, but I think it's Disney's
Indiana Jones or something.
I rode it about five times.
I don't know how to tell you how much fun it was.
I don't know how to tell you this, but it was really fun.
I don't know how to express it, but it was really fun.
I'm really glad we went because it was really good and it was raining at the time.
It was raining at the time, so the rides were pretty empty.
So it was really fun!
The one with the glowing teeth...
I think it was at the beginning.
I don't know.
I don't know... there was a light...
There was a light.
And maybe something white or...
I don't know, maybe something white or something reflective? I don't know.
But the teeth, they glow?
So, the first time I rode it...
Nonaka-chan, Emma, Yuna, when I got on the first time.
Emma and Yuna got on.
And we all rode together.
We were all like, "Wow!
They said, "Wow, that's great, that's great!
They were saying "wow".
Then one day...
Emma first looked at Yuna.
Emma was looking at Yuna first.
And when Yuna looked at Emma.
She was smiling.
I don't know why, but it didn't bother me before.
I don't know why, but it didn't bother me before, but suddenly it bothered me a lot that her teeth were shining.
I wondered if Nonaka-chan's teeth were shining too, so I turned to her and asked her to turn around.
Then I asked her to turn around, and she was laughing so hard that she was glowing.
So, you know, that was fun, and the ride was fun, but it was the fact that her teeth were glowing that made it fun.
I told Yuna and Nonaka, and they both laughed so hard, and they both said they wanted to see it light up too, so we all rode the ride just for that.
We were all laughing so much! I hope you guys get to see it when you go on it.
My nails were glowing, too, and my hands were all shiny, and yes, it was a little bit funny.
And when Nonoka turned around, she had a big smile on her face.
It was really funny.
I hope you all enjoy the ride.
Yes, the trio really likes to eat, don't they?
And they eat a lot.
That's why.
They had all been studying the food preferences, and they wanted to eat this and that, so they ate a lot.
We ate a lot of churros and dumpling buns.
And then I'll tell you what else we ate... chicken.
I ate chicken and drank hot cocoa because it was raining and it was so cold.
I remember drinking hot cocoa and eating a lot.
By all means.
I said "by all means." Gyoza-dog, gyoza-dog, gyoza-dog. It was so good.
They were amazing! They were so good!
It was so good, but I also had popcorn...
But... it's another bad day at Disney...
But I thought I'd probably gain a lot of weight when I got home.
I didn't gain any weight.
That's probably because I went on five rides.
And I was screaming so hard, and it was raining, and... you know that thing that spins around in the rain? The Sea.
I don't know... there's one that spins around in the rain.
And when it stopped raining...
And when it stopped raining, it was really empty, so...
So I got on it.
And...
It was scary, right?
Four out of three?
There's no one who can handle a lot of scary rides.
Everyone can ride it pretty well, but...
We were all a little scared.
So the first morning, we were all a little scared, but we were all a little scared.
When we got on that night, everyone was saying, "It's cold, it's cold, it's cold, it's cold.
Raging Spirits, maybe, at the end of the ride, it was really cold.
But I got used to it.
Everybody was riding so much.
We rode it about three times.
Really, really.
We rode it so much.
We're the ones who can get there just in time.
One ride is just a moment.
Raging Speights is a lot of fun.
I was so happy to be a Soiree Surrey for the first time.
It was really, really good.
I want you to ride it. Sit down.
I was laughing with Yuna the whole time!
It was really fun
Who suggested we go? What?
I think we talked about it in New Zealand when we were in the hotel together.
I think that's when we talked about going to Disney.
I think we went there.
It was kind of fun, wasn't it?
I'm looking forward to going to the Seek this month.
I like the Sea.
It was really fun.
I was able to make a lot of reservations with my partner.
I had a lot of fun.
I had a lot of partners.
Have you ridden the c gondola? Maybe not. No. I've ridden the c gondola.
How did you get on the two-seater? Oh, how did you get on the one where you have to take turns playing rock-paper-scissors-paper with each other? We took turns playing rock-paper-scissors, and each of us took a turn to ride the gondola.
It was so much fun.
Lately
Lately...
Yesterday
Yesterday was an interview day.
Afterwards
I went out to dinner with Yuna.
It's a very ordinary thing, but I went out to dinner with Yuna afterwards.
It's a super normal thing, but...
All three of us went to Instagram, so I'm really wanting to go there.
Please, please, please, please go!
Please go!
Oh, Yomiuriland, that's right, that's right, the open recording... but, you know, for those of you who came, the second part of the show, the second part of the show, we did that quirky intro...
We did that quirky intro, but you got it, didn't you?
You all understood it, didn't you?
I think they improved a lot.
After the show, Mr. Fujii told me that he really laughed out loud.
He said, "I don't understand.
I don't know, I don't know.
I'm sure I've done it, right?
I'm doing good, aren't I?
It was a great experience for me to answer and understand.
I felt I was getting better, but I didn't understand. You didn't understand?
But you know what, I didn't even understand the chichinpui. I didn't understand it anymore, I didn't know what I was doing.
But it was a lot of fun. See you next year!
I hope you all come again next year.
Oh, no, no, no!
I'm going to play until 50 minutes today.
We're going to play until 50 minutes today.
I'm already having a hard time deciding what songs to play.
I think I'm going to do karaoke.
What song do you want to sing right now?
Please comment what you want me to sing.
I'd appreciate it.
Please comment on what you want me to sing.
Mm-hm.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, and one more thing...
Please spread the word!
Today, too.
Let's see...
You know...
Do you know Atarayo?
She loves that song.
I wonder if you know it.
October, I forget you don't talk much.
Do you know her?
Do you know that song?
It's morning.
I mean, it's not morning.
I mean, we're already together.
Oh, this one's getting smaller.
Spread it around.
Spread the word!
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best
I'm gonna do my best.
Did you hear that?
Oh, you hear that?
Oh, I did it right away, it's so hard.
I think it's time for me to go.
Thank you for everything.
It's been fun.
Bye-bye.
Can you at least look at me one last time?
I didn't mean for it to end like this.
I should've seen it coming.
But then you change.
I'm going to catch it.
text at the foot of the page
me
I was walking down the street because tears were stinging my eyes
because you smile at me
If it hurts this much
I didn't want to know
You're always so kind Thank you for watching me
I'm sorry I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
I like the next one.
Oh, this... oh, if I had done it like this...
I was doing it like this, like this, like this, like this. You didn't put one of these on?
How hard can it be?
What do you think?
Uh...
Superhero.
Thank you.
I see.
Tooth snow like this.
Reminds me of Aya, too.
No, no, no...
Ugh...
Oh...
That's Airi Ki's "Everyday without you".
This isn't hard.
It's cute, isn't it?
What should I do?
Let's see...
Durr durr durr durr lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala lala 啦啦 啦啦
嗯Thank you for watching, you're my senior today
It's too bad
I honestly can't hear you every day without you
No doubt a peaceful love of heart to not stop in society
What is the omniscient and omnipotent listening
Oddly enough, if it were my mouth and other times of eternity
When I sleep, when I'm tired, when I'm fulfilled
What is your meaning
Meme that takes care of the world
me
mememe
I don't know if you can hear me if I don't do it like this, but I have to protect what I like, and this is my rule that I can't lose, no matter what someone says.
That I can make this water strong
I saw someone who was lost
Someday you'll have a memory of me
I'm gonna see you in your mind You can do it Thank you I'm going to make a chan-chan
If I sing like this, I won't be so tiny
Thank you for watchingMemories keep growing, I want to be with you forever, even if I'm a crybaby
I don't care if you're a crybaby
I'm so happy to have met you
I'm happy to have met you
Forever and ever
I wish it would last forever
Even though I can't take your hand, I still love you, and I'm at ease in your dreams
I say I don't want to wake up
memories, more memories, more memories
c I don't want to be around you anymore
Difficult, usually
It's hard, isn't it?
Me.
Where to ohhhh!
down
me
Can't you see? No.
No.
I'm blooming flowers
I wish my me time would stop 같이 가야지
죄송해요 지금 밸런스 잠깐만요me now
mmm.
I'm sorry
me
Ima nen
I'm sorry.
I know...
I want to sing with Aimyon
Let's see...
I wonder if I can do this
Aww...
Poo
I've left all my dreams, all my dreams I've left all my dreams I've left all my dreams I've left all my dreams I've left all my dreams
All my dreams, all my dreams, I left everything behind, the days of my life, the days when I silently loved someone
When the sky clears up, give me your love, give me your love, give me your love
Tears are for tomorrow, for new flowers, for meme
me
Hmm.
I'm glad to hear you got goosebumps.
I have goosebumps, too.
What do you mean?
Wait a minute.
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch.
Wood.
mmm...
Ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha.
Ah.
I made a mistake.
This is...
I'm sorry.
You're so close.
Here you go.
You're the one who said...
It's nice to hear you say that.
It's...
It makes me sad.
The magic that dissolves after good-bye
Pale and bittersweet
The flame of love
Neither friend nor lover I'm on the rise
Neither friend nor lover, I'm on the rise
I'm a blue fruit dreaming of the harvest day
I'm on the rise because I can't take one more step
Okay, okay, okay
I'm so impatient, Baby
Love, thank you
When you say thank you, it makes me kind of sad
The magic that doesn't break even after good-bye is faint and bittersweet
So play ball with life
I miss it so much
Oh, this just now
Why don't you go?
Please sing something I can understand
Oh, it's so nostalgic!
It was so long ago!
Surprise!
I want to sing just the chorus.
I wonder if it's possible to sing just the chorus...
I wonder where I am and where I am now
I'm looking back again and again
I stare back again and again
I hold a dead leaf to stop nausea
I drew a dream with my gnawing fingertips
I have wings but I can't fly, I'm afraid of becoming a prawn, it's hard to cross over, we're walking on a lonely dream
Good-bye is not a sad word
Each dream connects us me
me
me, me, me... it's too good song!
I'm gonna cry!
Let's see what else we got
Let's see what else is left
Oh my God!
Let's see what else is here
What else do you think happened?
I sang "Jennifer" before
Aimyon
Did I sing "Aimyon Jennifer"?
Oh, but there's one more thing... seven minutes left...
I'm going to sing one more song.
What is it?
I think I'm gonna listen to something.
I don't know.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no. Jeliba.
Then let's go to Jeliva.
Who the hell are you?
Who's Jennifer Jenifer?
Jennifer, Jennifer, Jennifer... you know everyone?
Jennifer...
No, Jennifer.
Sad.
I wonder if we've talked about this before.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. We've talked about this before.
I'm sorry, too much.
Sorry, too much.
Shrimp stew...
Mm-mm.
Mm-mm-mm.
Mmm...
mmm
nh-ha-ha
Ho-ho-ho!
Let's all work hard together tomorrow. Let's stand tall, the sun is smiling Breathe in the happiness
Be a super hero I'm a super hero You and I both have the power to be true from the bottom of our hearts
The wind is strong, it's an exciting morning... Good, good, that black shadow of a wimp
I'm trying to turn that black shadow of a weakling
I'm trying to make you an angel
All right
We're superheroes
Everybody
Tears
Hides
Trick Power
Even if I cry a little
I want to believe strongly
Here and now is the starting line
Staboo, everyone
Let's do our best with a smile on our faces
Okay, so suddenly, let's all do our best with a smile on our faces
So...
It's just a little while now...
I'll try to get used to it.
I'll try my best to get used to it.
I'll see you all in the showroom again, because it's so much fun to deliver karaoke.
I'll do my best to make it happen.
Thank you very much.
So, that's it.
Today's
Today's today's today's today's today's today's today's today's
I'd like to announce the ranking.
Next.
Oh, here it comes.
I don't know if I'm right, but I'm thrilled.
Thank you very much. And number four.
In fourth place...
Don Moride.
Thank you very much.
Third place, Mr. Monta.
In second place, Mr. Berg.
Thank you very much.
1st place, Mr. Tomoki
So, we have
4600 people.
I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, and I'm looking forward to seeing more and more Emmas.
I'm going to do my best to make Emma known to many people in the showroom, so please come and visit us again.
See you at the Kana level!
Please see the Kana level.
Look at the well in the museum!